STANDARD FOR LIFE
Man of God, help me!
My name is Mathabo Ramphomane from South Africa.
I am addicted to eating soil, maize meal, paper, erasers and cloth.
Please, Man of God, help me!
It started when it was raining outside and when I smelt the scent of the soil,
I felt like eating it.
These are the things I eat, Man of God. Please, help me!
For how long have you been eating these?
It has been ten years now, sir.
What efforts have you put in place to put an end to it?
I had tried many things, sir, but all to no avail.
Demonstrate to us how you have been eating it.
The cloth - I would take it and feel like putting it into my mouth.
Addicted to Eating Cloth
When it is wet, I would take it out.
This is the eraser that I eat.
Addicted to Eating Eraser
This is the paper, sir.
Addicted to Eating Paper
What is this?
It is the maize meal, sir.
Go ahead.
Addicted to Eating Maize Meal
What is the next item?
Soil.
What is this?
This is soil.
Addicted to Eating Soil
It tastes like normal food.
Do you like it?
Very much, sir.
Addicted to Eating Soil
I have been eating it for ten years, sir.
Addicted to Eating Soil, Maize Meal, Paper, Erasers and Cloth
Man of God, please help me.
That is why I am here; please help me!
I am from South Africa.
Addicted to Eating Soil, Maize Meal, Paper, Erasers and Cloth
Never a problem that Jesus Christ cannot solve.
Amen.
Once you believe, you will receive your deliverance and freedom from this evil spirit.
I believe, sir.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Speak out: Who are you?
Who are you?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ! Speak out!
I am Lucifer.
I am Leviathan.
I am Numeral.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
How many of you are in her?
We are a legion.
How do you operate in this body?
The father gave her to us.
Speak out!
The father gave her to us! Can't you see?
Stand right and talk!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
What have you done to her so far?
Come here and answer me!
Come here!
Who are you?
Bring down your hand and answer me.
What have you done to her?
We took her since she was born and she served us.
She serves satan; she is a high priest. Who is supposed to fill that position?
Come back!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Come back here!
Stop!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
What have you done to her career and health?
Nothing is showing for her.
How did you enter her body?
We took her when she was born.
What is your mission in this body?
She must come back!
To where?
She broke the code of the occult!
Where do you want her to come back to?
Where are you living?
We are in the spirit.
Speak louder.
What are the evil things you have done so far? Mention them.
We cause confusion.
We gave her sicknesses.
We cause rejection.
We steal everything!
What have you done to the family members?
I have killed them; I have taken everything from them.
You said, "Everything". Mention them.
What are the things you have taken?
I broke their finances; I gave them sicknesses.
I caused confusion; I caused hatred.
I caused everything and I made sure they will not serve God.
They will serve us.
This body has been addicted to some things. Who caused it?
I did it, of course.
Speak louder.
I did, of course!
What do you want to gain?
Either she serves us, either she serves satan, or she will die.
How do you want to go about that?
I will make sure that she will always be confused.
She will never have a backbone. Do you hear me?
Do you hear me?
Apart from this body, what other evil things have you done to other people?
We destroyed them - the so-called pastors, Christians, businessmen,
marriages, everything - you mention them!
How do you go about destroying the so-called pastors?
We use her body.
How?
Explain how?
Why should I explain myself to you?
In the name of Jesus, speak out!
Stand up and answer me!
How?
We use her eyes.
How do you use her eyes and what happens when you use them?
So that when she sees things, we will also see it.
Anytime she enters a place, we are there; we are seeing with her.
Anything she sees, we will see it with her.
If she has plans, if she goes into a shop, if she goes anywhere, we will see with her.
You are talking about pastors. How do you go about using their body?
We use them.
How?
We shut their eyes.
And what happens to them?
They can't serve God; they can't see us.
They cannot see you people?
Yes, they can't.
They will only see light.
We will appear as light using her
but by the time we catch them, they won't know it.
You have said you have destroyed businessmen.
How do you go about that?
Anytime we go into their shops, we take the money; we buy with it.
How do you go to their shops?
We use spirits; we transport them.
We use bodies; some of them don't see us. We use them, indirectly.
What happens to their businesses and finances?
What do you think?
Answer me!
They fall!
What do you gain in doing that?
It's our kingdom.
The more we kill people, the more we destroy, the more we gain.
Alright?
What do you gain?
We gain their spirits,
we gain ownership of them.
What is your mission here?
I don't know how this girl came.
Speak louder!
We tried killing her in the air but we couldn't.
How did you try to kill her in the air? What did you do?
We gathered the principalities when they reached the sea, to kill her.
Why is it that you don't like the name Jesus?
What has that name been doing to you people?
Because we are darkness;
we don't mix with light.
Anytime you mention that name, it destroys us; we cannot operate.
So, that name is light?
Yes!
And it destroys you people?
It's fire! It's burning me!
Now, she is here.
Why is it that you do not like The Synagogue Church of All Nations?
This girl has been following Prophet T.B. Joshua since 1998.
She wanted to come here but we stopped her.
This year, a stupid boy from nowhere gave her money.
She will watch Emmanuel TV the whole night and we cannot operate.
She will watch what?
She will watch the Prophet.
She will pray; she will do everything.
She will put him on her phone, everything.
When she watches the Prophet, what happens to you and your colleagues?
We can't see; we can't walk; we can't do anything.
Which prophet does she watch?
Prophet T.B. Joshua.
What is in Prophet T.B. Joshua that is destroying you people?
He is light.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Now she has come here, what do you want to do?
We will kill her.
How?
She will never release the secret.
What is the secret?
Speak out!
We put a snake inside her.
What is the purpose of the snake?
It is a part of lucifer in her;
we can locate her everywhere.
But now that she is here, the snake will go.
When the snake goes, what will happen?
She will be free.
How many of you have been working with her?
Millions.
We keep inviting.
We are only disturbed when she prays with you people.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
What happens to you people when she prays with Emmanuel TV?
We cannot operate.
I told you; we can't operate.
We become stuck; we can't see.
Who are you?
I'm Numeral.
I'm Lucifer.
I'm Leviathan.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Your end has come.
Right now.
I'm warning you.
Why?
I destroyed many of them who had tried.
Be free!
In Jesus' name.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
How are you?
I'm fine, sir.
You were telling us something that you normally eat these as normal food.
Can you identify them and taste them?
It is soil, maize meal, cloth, eraser and paper.
Ok. Go ahead.
Set Free From an Addiction to Eating Soil, Maize Meal, Cloth, Paper and Erasers
What is happening to you?
It doesn't have a taste.
It doesn't taste good anymore?
Take more. Take other ones.
Set Free From an Addiction to Eating Soil, Maize Meal, Cloth, Paper and Erasers
What is happening?
It is irritating, sir.
Ok. Take other ones.
Set Free From an Addiction to Eating Soil, Maize Meal, Cloth, Paper and Erasers
What is happening?
It is too dry.
What about the paper?
Set Free From an Addiction to Eating Soil, Maize Meal, Cloth, Paper and Erasers
It is paper, sir.
What is happening?
Why are you spitting them out?
It is irritating, sir.
Set Free From an Addiction to Eating Soil, Maize Meal, Cloth, Paper and Erasers
Do you like it?
No.
The Lord has set you free.
Thank you, sir.
In Jesus' name.
Thank You, Jesus!
Wash your mouth.
Wash your mouth and then go and eat normal food.
Thank You, Jesus! I'm free!
Set Free From an Addiction to Eating Soil, Maize Meal, Cloth, Paper and Erasers
Glory be to God.
After Miss Mathabo's deliverance from the addiction to eating soil, maize meal,
paper, erasers and cloth, she is given a cup of water to rinse her mouth
and is also served with a delicious meal of rice, salad and chicken.
This is the evidence that she is indeed free from the addiction
and now has appetite for normal food.
As she eats, she waves her hand in appreciation to what God Almighty has done in her life.
"Thank You, Jesus Christ" is a response from a happy heart.
Set Free From an Addiction to Eating Soil, Maize Meal, Cloth, Paper and Erasers
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Mathabo Ramphomane
and I am from South Africa.
I am 28 years old.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was
an addiction to eating soil, paper, erasers, clothes and maize meals.
Man of God, help me.
My name is Mathabo Ramphomane from South Africa.
I am addicted to eating soil, maize meal, paper, erasers and cloth.
Please, Man of God, help me
It started when it was raining outside and when I smelt the scent of the soil,
I felt like eating it.
These are the things that I eat, Man of God. Please help me!
For how long have you being eating these?
It has been ten years now, sir.
Addicted to Eating Cloth
When it is wet, I will take it out.
This is the eraser that I eat.
Addicted to Eating Eraser
This is the paper, sir.
Addicted to Eating Paper
What is this?
It is the maize meal, sir.
Go ahead.
Addicted to Eating Maize Meal
What is the next item?
Soil.
What is this?
This is soil.
Addicted to Eating Soil
It tastes like normal food, sir.
Do you like it?
Very much, sir.
Addicted to Eating Soil
I have been eating it for ten years, sir.
Addicted to Eating Soil, Maize Meal, Paper, Erasers and Cloth
Man of God, please help me!
That is why I am here; please help me.
I am from South Africa.
Last week, I was delivered through Wise Man Christopher.
Immediately the Wise Man started delivering me, the spirit started operating inside me.
The spirits of lucifer, leviathan and numeral started to manifest.
The spirit of lucifer is the spirit that is anti-Jesus, anti-Christ.
It is the spirit that causes conflict, confusion and all the horrible things
that you see happening in the world.
The second spirit that operated in me was the spirit of leviathan.
The spirit of leviathan is the old, ancient demon
that is responsible for all the marine activities.
For example, the spiritual husbands.
It operates the mermaids and the snakes that are in the rivers.
Most people don't know of those things but they do exist
and they all fall under the king, leviathan.
The third spirit that was operating in me was the spirit of numeral.
The spirit of numeral is the spirit that has all the statistics of the world
because it operates with numbers and the alphabet.
The reason being, that everything that is done in this world is
done using numbers and the alphabet.
Whether you code a name or you name a product,
everything will be done with regards to numbers and the alphabet.
So, it works mainly with possessing the minds of the people
and connecting to them through their names and numbers.
For example, on your ID, your birthdate has numbers
and your name has the alphabet so that was how satan would use the spirit of numeral
to get the database of the world.
I was trained by satan to sit in the cabinet because there is a protocol in the spiritual realm.
There is the trinity of satan.
The trinity of satan is satan, the beast and the false prophet.
The second step is the principalities, the powers, the rulers and the lords.
that rule the universe, including the world.
There are continental demons who monitor every single continent
and they are responsible for monitoring every single activity that goes on in the continent.
There are supervising demons who get directives from the continental demons
to guard every single area of the world - whether in the land, air or sea.
Then there are senior demons - those who are monitoring
towns, cities, and all the other areas within the continents.
Then we have junior demons who follow each and every human being.
Whether rich, young, old, the junior demons monitor will everything about those people
and they make sure to connect with the minds of people, to torment them.
They will cause things like the spirits of lying, lust, anger, bitterness, laziness.
All those spirits will be monitoring the minds of the people
and they will influence them.
They are regarded as the most important demons
because they are the ones who are involved in the day-to-day activities of human beings
and they have the power to invite worse demons than them.
So, the tools that the enemy would be using -
he would use every single mode of communication that human beings use.
For example, he can use music, the internet, 'men of God';
he can use every single person, the stakeholders in the community and world.
For example, the 'men of God', he would use them by making them to crave power instead of grace.
Because he would make sure that every single time they become famous,
and their churches and everything about them grows,
they would crave for more power and they would have pride.
At that time when they have pride, the evil spirits will come in and supply them with power
Now because of the pride, they would be blinded and not see the source of the power.
They would also use the people around the man of God.
If at all they cannot reach the man of God, they would use, for example, the children of the man of God,
the wife, the pastors, or other denominations in the church.
They would make sure that they caused frustration.
You would find that the pastor's children are wayward.
It is those spirits that are monitoring them, making sure that the man of God is frustrated.
They would always have no time with God.
They would always be frustrated and try to solve problems.
At the end of the day, the protection is gone, and they would enter and destroy the man of God.
We use fornication.
Fornication in the sense that when you are sleeping with somebody, there is a transfer of blood.
The time you sleep with someone - whether a prostitute or anyone else
that is not of the same religion as you, or just sleeping with anybody,
you will transfer blood into that person, and they will transfer blood into you.
If a man of God sleeps with a prostitute, the minute you sleep with them,
she would go and report back to the kingdom of darkness.
Whenever that prostitute, or whoever you slept with, is promoted in rank,
the man of God would be taken along with her.
That is why you find many men of God are destroyed today.
They are possessed but they are not aware of it
because they thought that they only slept with the person.
The internet - how they use the internet:
There are certain websites that they would post,
for example, music, pictures and the latest gadgets people use.
For example, they would use a picture:
You would not necessarily know that that picture is evil
but they would know that it is very evil.
We connect it with you if, for example, you have a weakness of laziness,
that demon in the picture on the internet will connect with your laziness
so that minute you look at that picture, it would invite more spirits
who would be transferred in you.
Many people don't know that the things that are posted on the internet have spirits;
they don't just act alone.
They act with spirits inside them.
Music - how we transfer music:
Music is a crowd puller; many artists are crowd pullers.
Artists that belong to the kingdom of darkness, the kingdom of satan,
any lyrics and songs are not sent alone but go with spirits.
Whenever you listen to their music, the lyrics may not say, 'satan',
but within them, because of the authority they are given in the kingdom of darkness,
they would transfer spirits and connect with your spirit.
If you don't have protection, they would possess you.
Many people are not aware that many artists belong to the kingdom of darkness.
We were in a meeting with the cohorts of the devil in hell.
So, this man came - I didn't know it was Jesus.
He was wearing a robe - it was red and looked like it was dipped inside blood.
It had a golden rope on this side.
He had holes in His hands and feet.
His face looked like somebody had beaten Him up.
He looked almost disfigured; you couldn't recognise Him.
He had a crown made of thorns on His head.
The minute I saw this man, I developed a curiosity to know Him
because whenever He came, everything would stop.
Not even Satan could move; he would just stop right there.
I went to Him, and when I touched Him, when He looked at my side, I felt love and compassion,
and those things I was not related to.
That's what made me decide to exit the kingdom of darkness.
Physically, I confessed to my mother that I had been serving satan.
Because she did not understand, my mother now called different pastors
to come and pray for me.
Most of the time, when they would pray for me, the spirits inside me would despise the man of God
because they would see that he had not gotten to the level I was at that time.
Many men of God that tried to pray for me were destroyed.
Some of them were fornicating, others were drunkards.
One day, my brother gave us the video cassette of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The first time I saw the prophet of God, I said to my mother,
"I have to meet this man; I believe this man can help me.
I believe he is the only one who can help me".
That is when I tried to come - since 1998, I have been trying to get here.
Recently, I was able to come to The SCOAN.
The men of God that came to deliver you - are you the one that attacked them, or was it your people?
It was the people that I was serving that were attacking the men of God
because I wanted to go out of the kingdom.
I was battling between me and them.
Anytime I would see the men of God, I would start to attack and did not have control over it.
They did not have a flame, light, or fire around them like the genuine men of God
or angels guarding them.
So, many of them are true men of God, but for most of them,
at each stage, they would use their weaknesses;
that is why they were not able to deliver me.
Is there anyone that could not deliver you, and you could not deliver them?
No, sir.
So, anybody that could not deliver you, you would deliver them?
Yes, sir
How did you deliver them?
Mainly, it was because they did not have the protection around them.
So, anytime they would pray for me, it would be as though I was delivered
but deep down I would know that I was not fully delivered.
I was still having the connection with the kingdom of darkness.
They would attack the men of God, causing confusion and frustration.
For some of them, they would break their marriages,
and cause havoc around the men of God who were trying to deliver me.
As a chief priest, I would get directives from satan to give assignments
to different levels of demonic forces, for example, to cause accidents, kill people
and cause havoc in the world.
The main reason why we were causing accidents and killing people
was because we ate human flesh and drank human blood.
The reason for eating human flesh and drinking human blood
was because life is in the blood.
We would eat that blood and flesh to gain more life and superiority over demons and human beings.
Every time I would watch the man of God through Emmanuel TV at home -
I would spend the night watching it and praying with the man of God, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Every time I would watch him, there would be peace inside me.
I decided to come because the difference between the man of God and all the other people,
who were trying to deliver me in the past,
is that the man of God is very humble and simple.
He has a heart for people and genuine love for people.
That is what brought me here.
Other people, when their ministry begins to grow, and they see God using them,
they become big headed and develop pride.
At the end of the day, it is all about them and not about God.
That is how I got to The SCOAN.
Now you are delivered.
The minute a child is born, in the kingdom of darkness,
they would take the bag containing the baby (placenta)
and make incantations and curse the child's life.
You would find that the child is initiated from birth.
That is why small children can kill big people.
People would wonder how they did it.
Parents should be conscious of what happens to their children.
I would advise everybody to be in the Lord Jesus
and to accept Him as their personal Lord and Saviour.
Without that, there is no protection, and they would suffer affliction from the enemy.
People of God, never take anything for granted
because satan can use anything and everything,
even things you think he cannot use.
People should seek the grace of God, instead of the power they are craving for
because you don't know the source of the power that you are going to get.
Wow! Thank you very much. Did you listen to that?
She said people seek power, and the Bible says, "Behold, I have given you power" already.
You are already born with power.
It is in you.
We cannot be greater than our processing.
Build this faith by hearing the Word.
When you hear the Word of God and obey it, faith grows.
So that faith is now the object to release the power.
That is the key
The switch.
You have a switch like this.
I want to switch this on.
It's easy. I switch it on.
That is faith.
I switch it on.
She is telling us that talking about power, you have the power.
But it is faith - by hearing the Word of God and obeying it, you have faith.
Your life will run smoother when you go by the Book.
Thank you, Man of God, I am free, and I am free forever, in the name of Jesus.
Ok, since your deliverance, what are your experiences whilst sleeping?
Before now, when I was at home, even my mother would fight because I would not sleep.
But since then, I have been sleeping very well, sir.
Before now, I could not balance between the physical life and spiritual life.
But now I can see that everything is finished, and now I am free in Jesus' name.
Thank You, Jesus!
Amen.
So what of your people?
Because, you are conscious of what you were doing.
This consciousness - there are many that are not conscious of what they are doing.
They possess them.
When they finish delivering them and tell them, "This is what you said", they say "No, I'm not the one".
But you - you were conscious of what you were doing.
You were there, you knew what you were doing.
You would do it physically.
Spiritually - yes, you were there.
How do you bring them to the light?
I will meet them and tell them the truth of the Gospel of the Lord Jesus Christ.
Today, 90% of these people are not conscious of what they are doing.
The moment they finish delivering them, and they are told, "You said this",
they will say, "No, over my dead body. I could never say that".
"You said you are doing it." - "No!"
"You said you are a snake" - "Snake? I'm a human being."
It means that they are not conscious of what they are doing.
Whereas 10% of them, like this sister, are conscious of what they are doing.
They are the possessors.
They afflicted the other people.
By attack, they can afflict you, and be using you and you would not know.
They will just take your image, go wherever they go, and do whatever they want to do.
Anybody that is crying there - the spiritualists see the people that attack them.
They will not see the people that use that image.
That is why today they keep attacking the wrong people.
They call the wrong people witches in the village and community.
Many people accused of being witches and wizards are not witches and wizards.
They are being afflicted.
The people that are witches and wizards, they are somewhere, hiding somewhere.
Even by the time people attack the accused witches and wizards, they will come and join them to attack.
This world is not my home
I'm just passing through
My treasures are laid up
Somewhere beyond the blue
The angels beckon me
From Heaven's open door
And I can't feel at home
In this world anymore